<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RentserviceBD</string>
    <string name="splashscreen_text">I’m from JFJ</string>
    <string name="signin_text">Login</string>
    <string name="welcome_page">Welcome To RentService</string>
    <string name="welcome_page_two">Rent online and get awesome delivered from stores
        to your home in as fast as 1 hour .</string>
    <string name="create_account">Create An Account</string>
    <string name="create_account_two">Fill your details </string>
    <string name="sign_in_page_text">Enter your phone number and
password to access your account</string>
    <string name="otp_page_text">Enter Verification Code</string>
    <string name="otp_page_text_one">We have sent SMS to your number</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="registr_here"><u>Register Here</u></string>
    <string name="forgot"><u>Forgot Password ?</u></string>
    <string name="Profile_address">Address<font color='#F10909'>*</font></string>
    <string name="Profile_Division">Division<font color='#F10909'>*</font></string>
    <string name="Profile_DiStrict">District<font color='#F10909'>*</font></string>
    <string name="Profile_Police">Police Station<font color='#F10909'>*</font></string>
    <string name="Terms_and_con">Advertisers And Users Are Responsible For Complying
        With All Applicable Laws And Regulations While Uploading Content, Text,
        And Images For Advertising On The Rent Service. Rental Service Is Not
        Responsible If All Content Is Illegal And Contains False Information.
        Advertisers And Users Warrant That Advertising Content Does Not Infringe Any Copyright,
        Proprietary Rights Or Other Rights Of Any Person Or Entity. Advertisers And Users Further Agree That The Rent Service Is Included From All Obligations, Liabilities And Claims Arising Out Of The Use Of The Services. Advertisers Agree That Their Submitted
        Content May Be Displayed On Rentservice Partner Sites In Accordance With Rentservice Terms.
        </string>

    <string name="About_one">
        	Advertisers And Users Are Responsible For Complying With All Applicable Laws And
        Regulations While Uploading Content, Text, And Images For Advertising On The Rent Service.
        Rental Service Is Not Responsible If All Content Is Illegal And Contains False Information.
        Advertisers And Users Warrant That Advertising Content Does Not Infringe Any Copyright,
        Proprietary Rights Or Other Rights Of Any Person Or Entity. Advertisers And Users Further
        Agree That The Rent Service Is Included From All Obligations, Liabilities And Claims Arising
        Out Of The Use Of The Services. Advertisers Agree That Their Submitted Content May Be Displayed On
        Rentservice Partner Sites In Accordance With Rentservice Terms.
    </string>
    <string name="About_two">
       	Rental Service reserves the right to cooperate with the appropriate authorities
        if any content violates applicable laws. For example,
        an ISP may identify advertisers or user identities. Also,
        IP addresses may be logged to ensure compliance.
    </string>
    <string name="About_three">
        	Rental Services will collect information from users and advertisers.
        It is a condition of using the Rent Service that each User and Advertiser
        grant and authorizes the Rent Service to collect and use information. Rental
        Service may use the information collected with its affiliate companies and any
        other persons for purposes of assisting and managing Rent Service and for purposes
        of Rent Service development, such as research,
        marketing, product development and planning.
    </string>
    <string name="About_four">
       	Rental Services may require payment for certain items and services such as membership packages,
        rental postings, rental searches, third-party advertising, posting ads in selected categories, etc.
        Advertisers can purchase vouchers to promote their ads from the Rent Service. Advertisers and users
        who voluntarily wish to post content (Paid Content) in exchange for rent services may be required to
        transfer information to a third party service provider, which may be governed by that party own rules.
        CONNECTION WITH ANY THIRD PARTY PROVIDERS IS DONE BY THE ADVERTISER AND USER AT ITS OWN RISK AND RENT SERVICES
        IS FREE FROM ANY RESPONSIBILITY IN CONNECTION THEREWITH.
        Rent Service shall not be obligated to provide any refund against any matter related to paid content.
    </string>
    <string name="About_five">
    	Rental Service reserves the right to change these terms and conditions. Such changes may
        be effective upon publication of the Rent Service. You are responsible for reviewing such changes.
        Your continued access to or
        use of the Rent Service will result in your acceptance of the following Terms.
    </string>
    <string name="Contact_Info">
    E-mail : rentservicebd@gmail.com
    </string>
    <string name="Contact_Info_one">
    Phone : +8801974206106
    </string>
    <string name="Contact_Info_Address">
    Address : 13,R N Road, Jessore Sadar, Jessore.
    </string>


</resources>